Welcome back. So, um hopefully you
survived the section on selection and if
statements and turnary operators. Um
this will test the sum of those skills
that you've learned. So I left so at the
top I want the typical comment your name
and a brief description of what the
program does. Um and then what I want
you to do is I want you to write a
program that takes four inputs. Each
input should be a letter grade and then
I want you to convert that letter grade
to its corresponding grade point value.
Uh so if someone enters an A, you give
them 4.0, A minus 3.7. I've got the
table further down and we'll all scroll
down to it in a minute. For simplicity,
assume that all classes are worth
exactly three credits. Um and then I
want you to take all four grade points
and calculate a GPA. Um, after you
calculate your GPA, I want you to
display a message based on if the GPA is
3.3 uh or higher, 2.3 to 3.3 or 2.3 or
below. Um, you will note that this
assignment is probably a little
repetitive when you're programming it.
Uh, that is so that you can appreciate
some of the cool features that we're
going to talk about later that will make
this task a lot easier. This task and
other tasks like it a lot easier. Um,
with what we learn in the future, you'll
be able to complete this assignment in
very few lines of code. But for now, the
repetition should give you a lot of
practice with selection. And then here
is the grade table. All right, good
luck.